Danielle Ragas

danielleragas.me ragasdanielle@gmail.com +1 604 353 7945

Skills

Storyboarding Sketching Graphic Design Illustration Motion Graphics Video Editing Writing

Tools

Adobe Creative Suite Autodesk Maya HTML/CSS Unity 3D Final Cut Pro

Interests

Gaming

I love RPGs and nonlinear gameplay. Currently playing Assassin's Creed Odyssey and Prey.

Illustration

I've created original and fan work under the artist name Tsuyuus since 2014.

Education

BA in Design

Simon Fraser University

2013 - August 2019

About

I'm an artist from Vancouver with a passion for illustration, animation, video editing, and storytelling. I strive to create memorable experiences, and I can bring my creativity and strong communication skills to any project and position.

Experience

Associate Artist / BioWare

September 2017 - August 2018

Produced ten storyboards for cinematic cutscenes and gameplay moments for two different projects.

Routinely presented boards to writers, animators, and designers to identify problems in scenes, come up with appropriate solutions, and iterate on feedback.

Artist / Beep

Video Game / January 2019 - April 2019 / Academic

Created concept art, storyboards, game assets, and environment art for a 3D adventure puzzle game.

Animated characters and the opening and ending cutscenes.

Animator and Editor / Amorphous

Short Film / January 2016 - April 2016 / Academic

Modeled and animated the main character and two environments for a 3 minute long 3D animated film about an astronaut on an alien planet.

Compiled rendered shots together and added visual effects such as backgrounds and holographic screens.

Marketing Assistant / Applied Biological Materials

September 2016 - December 2016

Designed various website assets and print material for both public and in-house use according to the company's existing style guide.

Recorded audio for and animated two 8 minute videos illustrating biotechnology concepts for the company's YouTube channel.